What did you come up with? The output warranted is
a typical case of needing multiple loops, in this
case, multiple for loops, because we have three
levels to account for and three items to account
for within those levels. I decided to store both
these sets of items in lists on lines 1 and 2,
specifically one list for the items and one
for the levels. Then, I have a for loop for
each level as, in the output, the levels, not the
items, are listed multiple times before going to
the next item. That is one tip for multiple loops.
Whatever needs to be listed in a group needs to be
in the outer loop. Within the for loop for levels
on line 3, I have another for loop for items on
line 4. In the output, you’ll notice that one item
is skipped: the rock on level 2. If that condition
is true, I have an if statement on lines 5 and
6 that uses the continue keyword to continue the
loops. Else, on lines 7 and 8, I use an f-string
to format the message to include both the item and
the displayed level. And I will run this code to
get the desired output. I encourage you to take
breaks from the videos and workbook projects
when needed and make some small code snippets
that apply the concepts you are learning in this
course and to something you can relate to. If I
was learning Python, I would make code examples
related to my interests. Try doing the same,
and you will find that the learning process will
be a little smoother as you learn these concepts.